(Howard:)Just flip the switch
(Howard:)until the lights on the drone
change to solid yellow.
(Sheldon:)All right,
that seems simple enough.
(Sheldon:)Initiating calibration sequence.
(Sheldon:)One, two, three, four,
(Sheldon:)five, six, seven,
eight, nine, ten.
(Sheldon:)Well, I suppose ten
is technically "at least ten."
(Sheldon:)But they're still getting
at least one angry letter.
(Howard:)Now I rotate
it horizontally
on its center axis until
the lights turn green.
(Sheldon:)Initiating rotation sequence.
(Sheldon:)Don't look at me, initiate.
(Raj:)Oh...
What does red
and yellow mean?
(Howard:)It means the
calibration failed.
(Howard:)We have to start over.
(Sheldon:)Oh. Very well.
(Sheldon:)Reinitiating
calibration sequence.
(Sheldon:)One, two, three, four,
(Sheldon:)five, six,
seven, eight, nine, ten...